safexbikes.com 2015-12-15

# Safexbikes Motorcycle Superstore - Our Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which SZ Motorcycle Industries collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the safexbikes.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by sz motorcycle industries. 

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the siteplace an orderfill out a formsubscribe to the newsletter and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information,   
Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.   
We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

### How we use collected information

SZ motorcycle industries collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes: 

  * To improve customer service
  * Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To personalize user experience
  * We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * To process transactions
  * We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature
  * To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * To send periodic emails

The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users. 

### Changes to this privacy policy

SZ motorcycle industries has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page,. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

### This website uses Google AdWords

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven't completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone's past visits to the [CLIENT NAME] website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google's privacy policy. You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want to you can [opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) or [permanently using a browser plugin.](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/intl/en/plugin/)

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: 

  * SZ motorcycle industries
  * safexbikes.com
  * SZ Motorcycle Industries, 1529/27, Naiwala, Karol Bagh, NEW DELHI - 110005
  * 9873151505,9210189229
  * info@safexbikes.com

## Verified Parts

_Get quality parts from trusted sellers only_

## Best prices

_Get maximum discounts offered in the market_

## Fast Delivery

_Get parts within 7-10 business days_

Why shop at Safexbikes.com Motorcycle Superstore?

22 years of Acquiring an Outstanding Reputation for Service and Quality Safexbikes have some superior products for motorcycles in store for you. Everything from Front Mudguards and Front Fairings to Side Panels and Tail Cowls, Indicators, Head Lights, Engine Parts, Gear Parts, Clutch parts, you ask it we have it all. Our products are made from nothing less than the best materials, and our prices are great as well. So if you want the best products, be sure to come to us. We are the first Indian Company to sell Motorcycle parts and accessories online. "BY Harpreet Sethi" 

###  Buy Motorcycles, Bikes and Scooter Parts and Accessories Online 

Online buying of Parts and Accessories for your bike helps you make the right choice at right price. We offer all the essential parts for your bike along with the trendy accessories and racing gears. Ours is the Store that offers all of the reliable brands in Motorcycle parts and accessories industry. We provide a the Shopping experiance that is simpler, easier, faster and always Online. At Safexbikes, we understand bikers and bikes needs better, and therefore, we strive to offer you the best of quality and finish. We showcase products from all categories such as Spare Parts, Body Parts, Accessories, Graphics, Modification Parts, Racing Gears, Riding Casuals, Batteries, Helmets and other safety products . 

No matter what style of motorcycle you ride, Safexbikes.com Motorcycle Superstore has the gear you need. Safexbikes.com Motorcycle Superstore offers the largest online selection of motorcycle gear, motorcycle apparel, motorcycle parts and motorcycle accessories. You'll find the guaranteed lowest prices on everything from motorcycle helmets, motorcycle jackets and motorcycle boots to motorcycle tires, motorcycle luggage and motorcycle covers. Offering free shipping options, safe and secure ordering, and no hassle returns, Safexbikes.com Motorcycle Superstore is the web's premier motorcycle outfitter in India. 

Recent Customer Testimonials

by ( ) on
